<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dylan Craven</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dylan Craven</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data/</guid>
      <description>Open Data I collected a moderate amount of new data as part of my graduate research in Panama, but more recently have benefitted enormously from the generosity of others. All data sets are open access, and are available via DataDryad or Figshare. I am a member of Open Traits.
  Panama Secondary Forest Traits: 17 traits measured on 55 woody species and up to 1700 individuals per trait.
Download here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/equipo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/equipo/</guid>
      <description>Equipo Investigador Principal Dylan Craven, Profesor Asociado, Centro de Modelación y Monitoreo de Ecosistemas, Universidad Mayor
Dylan es un ecológo de bosques que investiga patrones temporales y espaciales de la biodiversidad y sus implicaciones, y usa aproximaciones de la ecología funcional y la macroecología para abordar esos temas. Para más información sobre sus intereses de investigación, consulte la páginas de sus publicaciones
Asistente de Investigación Valentina Pérez, Ingeniera forestal, Universidad Mayor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/join/</guid>
      <description>Oportunidades Buscamos crear y mantener un grupo de investigación diverso, inclusivo y sobretodo apasionado por la biodiversidad, que está comprometido a aplicar lo que aprendemos para mejorar el mundo. Estamos comprometidos a guiar y apoyar a l@s integrantes del grupo a lograr sus metas profesionales.
Pre-grado
PhD
Post-docs
Participantes en un curso de servicios ecosistémicos en paisajes del trópico, Panamá
Estudiantes de pre-grado Eng general, ofrecemos temas en dos áreas: i) ecología funcional y ii) macro-ecología.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Google Scholar | Publons
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have access to a PDF, please send me an e-mail!
2020 2019 2018 2017 2016 2015 2014 2013 2011 2010 2009 2007
2020 Craven, D., Sande, M.T. van der, Meyer, C., Gerstner, K., Bennett, J.M., Giling, D.P., Hines, J., Phillips, H.R.P., May, F., Bannar‐Martin, K.H., Chase, J.M. &amp;amp; Keil, P. (2020) A cross-scale assessment of productivity–diversity relationships. Global Ecology and Biogeography, 29:1940–1955. doi:10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Functional Biogeography
Island biogeography
Diversity - Stability
Secondary succession in tropical and temperate forests
Drivers of functional diversity of woody plants and consequences for carbon storage Identifying the drivers of biodiversity and their relationships with ecosystem functioning across large spatial scales is essential for improving the conservation and management of natural ecosystems. Chile is a unique natural laboratory for studying spatial patterns of biodiversity’s multiple facets, given its great diversity in environmental conditions and topography and unique biogeographic history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Biodiversity | Functional Ecology &amp;amp; Biogeography Dr. Dylan Craven Centre for Ecosystem Modeling and Monitoring, Universidad Mayor We explore drivers of temporal and spatial patterns of biodiversity and biodiversity change and their consequences, mostly in grassland and forest ecosystems. We are based in Chile, whose unique geography and climate provide a compelling template to address the following questions:
i) How do ecological and historical drivers jointly shape biodiversity patterns?
ii) How do biodiversity and biodiversity-dependent ecosystem functions vary across temporal and spatial scales?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
