<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dylan Craven</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dylan Craven</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a plant ecologist interested in temporal and spatial patterns of biodiversity change and its implications. I am particularly fascinated by the role of biodiversity in driving the capacity of ecosystems to resist and recover from global change drivers, such as land-use change and biological invasions. I examine these topics using experimental and observational studies and synthesis, focusing on the following questions:
i) How do biodiversity and biodiversity-dependent ecosystem functions vary across temporal and spatial scales?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Biodiversity patterns across islands at local and biogeographical scales Island ecosystems sustain a large proportion of global plant diversity, yet are critically imperiled due to global change. They are also a natural laboratory that can be used to examine how facets of biodiversity, ecosystem functioning, and biological invasions change from local to biogeographical scales. I am compiling a database of forest plots on islands across the Pacific Ocean to address these questions, in collaboration with Holger Kreft (U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Google Scholar| Publons
Batterman, S. A., L. O. Hedin, M. van Breugel, J. Ransijn, D. J. Craven, and J. S. Hall. 2013. “Key Role of Symbiotic Dinitrogen Fixation in Tropical Forest Secondary Succession.” Nature 502 (7470): 224–7. https://doi.org/10.1038/nature12525.
 Bernhardt-Romermann, Markus, Lander Baeten, Dylan Craven, Pieter De Frenne, Radim Hédl, Jonathan Lenoir, Didier Bert, et al. 2015. “Drivers of Temporal Changes in Temperate Forest Plant Diversity Vary Across Spatial Scales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>