<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Home</title>
    <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.dylancraven.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>¡Únete!</title>
      <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/join/</guid>
      <description>Oportunidades Buscamos crear y mantener un grupo de investigación diverso, inclusivo y además, apasionado por la biodiversidad, y que está comprometido a aplicar lo que aprendemos para mejorar el mundo. Estamos comprometidos a guiar y apoyar a l@s integrantes del grupo a lograr sus metas académicos y profesionales.
Pre-grado
PhD
Post-doctorados
Participantes en un taller de servicios ecosistémicos en paisajes del trópico, Panamá
Estudiantes de pre-grado En general, ofrecemos temas en dos áreas: i) ecología funcional y ii) macro-ecología.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Inigo Montoya. I have the following qualities:
I rock a great mustache I&amp;rsquo;m extremely loyal to my family What else do you need?
my history To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m having some trouble remembering right now, so why don&amp;rsquo;t you just watch my movie and it will answer all your questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipo</title>
      <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/equipo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/equipo/</guid>
      <description>Dylan Craven, Profesor Asociado, Universidad Mayor Ecológo, Yale University (School of the Environment)
Dylan investiga patrones temporales y espaciales de la biodiversidad y sus implicaciones, y usa aproximaciones de la ecología funcional y la macroecología para abordar esos temas. Dylan también está afiliado con el Data Observatory, donde busca impulsar un nuevo modelo de ciencia enfocado en el uso de datos abiertos para potenciar la investigación de la biodiversidad en Chile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data</title>
      <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/data/</guid>
      <description>Our laboratory is committed to making the data that we collect available publicly. All data sets are open access, and are available via DataDryad or Figshare. Dylan is a member of the Open Traits Initiative.
Rasgos-CL: 23 traits compiled from literature for 718 woody species in Chile.
Download here
Panama Secondary Forest Traits: 17 traits measured on 55 woody species and up to 1700 individuals per trait.
Download here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/publications/</guid>
      <description>Recent publications A rigorous synthesis of coastal lomas
Regional data sets can fill gaps in global trait databases
Dispersal and speciation shape the functional diversity of Tenerife
Publications Also see Google Scholar for Dr. Craven&amp;rsquo;s publications.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have access to a PDF, please send me a request via e-mail.
van Breugel, M., et al. (including Craven, D.). (2024) Feedback loops drive ecological succession: towards a unified conceptual framework. Biological Reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dylancraven.com/page/research/</guid>
      <description>Muestreo de rasgos funcionales en Chile
Resiliencia de la flora del Valle de Aconcagua
Experimento de biodiversidad y función ecosistémica
Functional Biogeography
Island Biogeography
Impacts of extreme droughts
Diversity - Stability
Resilience of tropical and temperate forests
Drivers of functional diversity of woody plants and consequences for carbon storage Identifying the drivers of biodiversity and their relationships with ecosystem functioning across large spatial scales is essential for strengthening the conservation and management of natural ecosystems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
